{"data":[{"question":"Great changes ___ in the country, and a lot of railway stations ___.","a":"have taken place, have been set up","b":"have been taken place, have been set up","c":"were taken place, were set up","d":"have taken place, have set up","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n+ First blank: active voice \n+Second blank: passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you think we should call his old teachers and friends as soon as he ___ in town?","a":"is arrived","b":"will be arrived","c":"will arrive","d":"arrives","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense \n- Active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I promise that the matter will ___.","a":"be taken care of","b":"be taken care","c":"take care of","d":"take care","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple future tense+ passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"That dinner was the most delicious meal we ___.","a":"have had","b":"would have","c":"have ever had","d":"had never had","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n- Ever= at any time","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Peter ___ his leg when he ___ in a basketball game against another school.","a":"was breaking, was playing","b":"broke, played","c":"was breaking, played","d":"broke, was playing","answer":"4","explain":"\n-Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the past was interrupted. The interruption is usually a shorter action in the Simple Past. \n- First blank: Simple past tense\n- Second blank: simple past continous tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"These teenagers ___ our soccer team.","a":"are belonged to","b":"are belong to","c":"belong of","d":"belong to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense- active voice \n- Belong to: if something belongs to someone, they own it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't get off the bus until it ___.","a":"stopped","b":"has stopped","c":"shall stop","d":"will stop","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n- = When the bus has stopped, you can get off ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll begin the dictation when you ___ ready.","a":"will be","b":"shall be","c":"have been","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense \n- Future tense + when simple present tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"This is a map of the airport that ___ in my home town.","a":"has been set up","b":"has set up","c":"is set up","d":"was set up","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n- Passive voice: have\/has been pp","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"We'll go with them as soon as we ___ our task.","a":"shall finish","b":"will finish","c":"finished","d":"finish","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense \n- Future tense + as soon as simple present tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}